export let decode = [
    {
        question: `Who said "I'm gonna make him an offer he can't refuse"?`,
        answer: () => 'godfather'
    },
    {
        question: `Toto, I've a feeling we're not in ...... anymore.`,
        answer: () => 'kansas'
    },
    {
        question: 'A census taker once tried to test me. I ate his liver with some fava beans and a nice .......',
        answer: () => 'chianti'
    },
    {
        question: 'Elementary, my dear ......',
        answer: () => 'watson'
    },
    {
        question: 'To infinity and ......',
        answer: () => 'beyond'
    },
    {
        question: 'Red right ....',
        answer: () => 'hand'
    },
    {
        question: 'Hannah + Mikkel',
        answer: () => 'jonas'
    },
    {
        question: 'aHR0cHM6Ly9kcml2ZS5nb29nbGUuY29tL2ZpbGUvZC8xSlhhR2xmX2l3QTZMS084aGlENngtVVdqNmVPX053V3kvdmlldz91c3A9c2hhcmluZw==',
        answer: () => 'mag'
    },
    {
        question: 'aHR0cHM6Ly9kcml2ZS5nb29nbGUuY29tL2ZpbGUvZC8xQVJtZmpyRzhudFpfV3VadEp3UndxR2p0cEdyQVNzOEYvdmlldz91c3A9c2hhcmluZw==',
        answer: () => '34558914442'
    },
    {
        question: 'Find the white rabbit',
        answer: () => localStorage.getItem('white_rabbit')
    }
]